var football = [
	{
		front: 'Chargers',
		back: 'Los Angeles'
	}, {
		front: 'Rams',
		back: 'Los Angeles'
	},{
		front: '49ers',
		back: 'San Francisco'
	}, {
		front: 'Raiders',
		back: 'Oakland'
	}, {
		front: 'Seahawks',
		back: 'Seattle'
	}, {
		front: 'Cardinals',
		back: 'Arizona'
	}, {
		front: 'Broncos',
		back: 'Denver'
	}, {
		front: 'Texans',
		back: 'Houston'
	}, {
		front: 'Cowboys',
		back: 'Dallas'
	}, {
		front: 'Saints',
		back: 'New Orleans'
	}, {
		front: 'Patriots',
		back: 'New England'
	}, {
		front: 'Eagles',
		back: 'Philidelphia'
	}
];

module.exports = football;